https://www.filklore.com/wordpress/alexa-skills/alexa-skills-privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Alexa Skills Privacy Policy
Filklore – Alexa Skills Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Filklore collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from Users of its Alexa Skills.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users of the Alexa Skills provided. The information will be held against a User ID made available by Amazon. We have no way to trace the actual identity of our Users, unless they choose to name themselves as a response to one of the Alexa Skills.
The information we collect
Only information given by the User in the Alexa Skill itself is collected.
Currently, personal information is restricted to:
Alexa Skill
Personal Information
Meat Meter
None
Posh Games
None
Pill Tray
A log of medications taken
Advanced Guitar Tuner
None
User of your personal information
Personal information is used only for the express purpose it is provided, within the Alexa Skill.
Retention of personal information
Personal information is only retained for as long as it is required for the purpose it is provided, to maintain the desired functionality within the Alexa Skill.
If you disable the Alexa Skill, your information will no longer be available to you, even if you re-enable the skill (as this changes your unique Amazon ID). Unused data will be automatically purged within 12 months
Sharing your personal information
We do not share any information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using our Alexa Skills, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Alexa Skills.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
This document was last updated Jul 4, 2020 @ 10:02 am.
